Romeu Fialho

romeubaptistafialho.dev@gmail.com

+351 967092983

linkedin.com/in/romeu-fialho-4592541ba

https://romeufialho.github.io/

Summary

I am a Gameplay Programmer experienced with C#, C++ and cooperating with designers and artists to create gameplay features and mechanics in Unity or Unreal Engine. Previously studied base programming languages like C as well as Operative Systems, Computer Hardware and Web Development.

Experience

Game Developer

Snake Marmalade Studios

Nov 2020 - Jan 2021 (3 months)

- ► Developed Marmalade Thief, using GB Studio.
- ► Helped with Programming, Level Design and story-line.

Game Programmer

WitchCatGames

Feb 2021 - Jul 2021 (6 months)

- ► Developed Lyzzy, using Unity.
- Responsible for all Programming related tasks and implementation of animations, UI and sound.

Game Programmer

Monsoon Games

Feb 2022 - Sep 2022 (8 months)

- ► Developed Gulp, using Unreal Engine 4.
- Responsible for all Programming related tasks and implementation of UI and sound.

Game Programmer

Freelance

Sep 2020 - Present (2 years 5 months)

- Developed indie games and experiences
- Keen to working as a team

Education

Polytechnic of Leiria

Bachelor's Degree, Games and Multimedia

2020 - 2023

Mainly focused on programming with C# and C++.

Game development in Unreal Engine and Unity.

Other aspects related to Game Design, Art, Sound Design, and Marketing & Business.

Escola Secundária Rafael Bordalo Pinheiro

Curso Profissional, Gestão e Programação de Sistemas Informáticos 2017 - 2020

C, Web Dev, SQL, Java, Computer Hardware and Software, Computer Networks

Skills

Game Development • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Unity • Unreal Engine • Desenvolvimento de jogos eletrônicos • Programação orientada a objetos (POO) • Unreal Engine 4 • C++ • C# • Arquitetura de computadores